

Pronouns: she/her

Email: emma.walker2410@gmail.com
Mobile: 0498 666 015 (text preferred)

A Newcastle based university student seeking Casual Employment/ Summer Internships

Confident, hardworking, resilient, passionate, and articulate individual with commended ability to work with others to achieve set outcomes.

## **Description**

Emma has held a gpa of 6.3 with the completion of 16 courses, aka 160 units in the Bachelor degree of Software Engineering (Honours), and is currently in her third year of this program of study at the University of Newcastle. She has experience using Canva. As outlined below, Emma is an ideal candidate for your software needs.

# **Job Experience**

July 2023 - present

The University of Newcastle- PASS Instructor: COMP1140 and ENGG1500

- Organised sessions for students to attend to assist them in their studies of the course
- Created worksheets each week based on lecture and lab content
- Help students improve their analytical skills, motivation, and study habits
- Discuss feedback on the course with the professor of the course in weekly meetings
- Worked on various admin things each week including submitting worksheets and attendance
- To obtain this job you must be passionate about learning and have achieved high results in the course

February 2023 - present

The University of Newcastle- Student Success Partner Mentor

- Conducted outreach calls to commencing students to establish contact
- Mentored multiple first year students individually and supported their transition to university
- Provided guidance on effective study skills and time management
- Referred students appropriately to student support such as Program Advisors, PASS, IT, UNSA, etc.

November 2020- February 2023

**Woolworths Cardiff-** Fresh Service Team Member (deli)

- Sales assistant
- Cleaning/stock prep
- Communicate and interact with customers to provide them with a good experience while getting groceries
- Can lead or assist in a team or individually with closes

April 2019

**Boeing Work Experience Placement** 

#### Education

February 2021 - present

University of Newcastle, NSW, Australia - Bachelor of Software Engineering (Honours) - year 3

October 2016 - October 2020

Warners Bay High School, Warners Bay, NSW, Australia - year 8-12

#### **Achievements**

- Uni Grades: majority HD D
- Highschool Grades: High Outstanding
- Outstanding Service and Leadership award- Jodie Harrison MP
- College Commendation List 2022 University of Newcastle
- WBHS Gold Award, Year 12 Outstanding Achievement
- Year 12 merit award- Software, Design and Development
- Bronze level in The Duke of Edinburgh's Award

#### **Volunteer Work**

- Current team member and coordinator for High Ping Valorant team in the UON Esports Club
- 2019-2020 Warners Bay High School Vice Captain
- 2020 Sport House Captain
- Helping a blind peer with trials and HSC being a scribe and reader
- Peer Support Leader (helped year seven students adjust to high school)
- Helping younger students with homework in afternoons
- Helped Fundraise \$1000 for the 2020 Bush fires

### **Interests/Extracurricular Activities**

- Traditional art (watercolours, acrylics, gouache, clay)
- Digital art and graphic design (with Canva, Adobe suite products, and Procreate)
- Photography
- Guitar
- Video Game design and Playing competitive and cosy games, books, musicals
- Machine Intelligence and Database Design as extra courses
- Crafting (crocheting hats, making instruments, making cosplays)

### **Personal Qualities and notes**

- Excellent skills in self-management
- Strong leader in projects/ strong leadership skills
- Digital literacy and software skills: including experience with Object Oriented Programming, Database and Information Management, and Data Structures using Python, Java, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, React, SQL, etc (familiar with Git)
- Brings a cheerful positive/ can-do attitude/ good work ethic
- Analytical thinker/ problem solver
- Enjoyable for others to be around/approachable/friendly
- Marvellous soft skills. Very articulate, outgoing and confident in public speaking
- Goal oriented, committed, and responsible, organised
- Team player, fast learner
- Currently working on a React program as a group project in SENG3150
- American Born, Australian citizen by descent ie has Australian working rights being Australian
- Deaf in one ear

# **Referees Upon Request**